<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<entries>
	<entry>
		<date>11/15/07</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/11-15-07_800x600.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/11-15-07_120x90.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Pesto, Mozzarella, Roasted Red Peppers, Sun-Dried Tomatoes, Red Onions, and Kalamata Olives on Thin Crust</title>
		<entryHtml>
			I opted for a thinner crust on this pizza, using about 3/4 
			of the volume of a normal dough ball for the same size pizza.
			Jennifer liked this one a lot.  She said it was the best one
			I have ever made.  She's said that a few times, so either I 
			am getting better at this, or she has a short memory.  I think 
			the former is true and not the latter (she remembers everything). 
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<date>10/22/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/10-22-07_800x600.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/10-22-07_120x90.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Garlic Butter, Green Peppers, Pineapple, Chicken, Red Onions, and Goat Cheese</title>
		<entryHtml>
			This was a fairly decent pizza.  It was a little on the greasy side.
			It is possible to put too much garlic butter on, and I think 
			that's what happened with this one.  Regardless, this is a 
			fantastic topping combination.  I remember the leftovers from 
			this one being pretty good.  
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<date>10/08/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/10-8-07_800x600.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/10-8-07_120x90.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Garlic Butter, Mozzarella, Bell Peppers, Tomatoes, and Kalamata Olives</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Pizza is always a good thing.  Even if it seems like it's
			the same pizza you've had a thousand times.  It still rocks.
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	
	
	<entry>
		<date>09/30/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/P9300001_800x600.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/P9300001_120x90.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Marinara, Mozzarella, Yellow Bell Peppers, Red Onions, Tomatoes, and Capers</title>
		<entryHtml>
			What a beautiful pie!  We decided to add capers to this one
			at the last minute, and that turned out to be 
			what made this pizza so good.  I went back to bread flour
			for this pizza.  I was feeling lazy when I made the dough and 
			didn't knead it as much as I usually do.  The result was
			very limp, delicate dough that wasn't very chewy after being
			cooked.  Still, the toppings more than made up for the 
			dough.  
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>09/25/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/P9250001_800x600.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/P9250001_120x90.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Marinara, Mozzarella, and Roma Tomatoes</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Ho, hum.... I was kind of bored by this one.  We just 
			didn't put a ton of energy into this pizza; it was kind of
			a normal pie with nothing very outstanding to speak of. 
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>09/18/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/9-18-07_800x600.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/9-18-07_120x90.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Garlic Butter, Basil, Mozzarella, Bell Peppers, Tomatoes, and Kalamata Olives</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Another pizza where we enjoyed fresh ingredients from the farmer's market.  We 
			already had a freeze here, so it's likely that were not going to see much more
			life at the market.  We're enjoying it while we can!
			I used regular flour for this pizza (I usually use bread flour or whole wheat flour) 
			and I was pleased with the change.  I really, really kneaded the dough this time; I'm 
			sure that has something to do with why the dough came out so well.  I also let the crust
			sit out and rise for about an hour after shaping it, and the final result was a light, 
			airy pizza crust that was pleasantly crisp on the bottom yet chewy throughout.   Mmmm..... 
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>09/10/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/9-10-07_800x600.JPG</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/9-10-07_120x90.JPG</thumbImg>
		<title>Garlic Butter, Basil, Mozzarella, Bell Peppers, and Red and Yellow Heirloom Tomatoes</title>
		<entryHtml>
			This pizza was straight from the farmers market.  I guess we had so much stuff
			from there we needed to eat it somehow.  We didn't even plan on having pizza, it 
			just kind of happened.  I sincerely enjoyed the tartness of the red tomatoes and
			how they contrasted with the sweet, buttery flavor of the yellow tomato.  In combination
			with fresh basil and green bell pepper, this was a pretty good pizza.  
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>08/18/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/8-18-07_1_800x600.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/8-18-07_1_120x90.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Marinara, Mozzarella, Red Onions, Green Bell Peppers, and Pepperoni</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Ah, it is not often I get to enjoy pepperoni on my pizza.  This 
			was a treat!  We invited Jen's parents over for dinner, and that
			was my excuse to buy some nice pepperoni for this pizza. 
			Needless to say, this was a classic pizza.  Definitely good
			re-heated as well.  I was glad that there were leftovers - hell yeah!
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>	
	<entry>
		<date>08/18/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/8-18-07_2_800x600.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/8-18-07_2_120x90.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>1/2 Marinara &#38; Mozzarella; 1/2 Marinara, Mozzarella, Green Peppers, Red Onions, and Artichoke Hearts</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Half of this pizza was for Jen's Grandmother Marie.  She
			loves cheeze pizza, plain and simple.  Jen, on the other hand,
			likes veggies a lot. I'm not crazy about artichokes, but we 
			had some left over from some other dinner and Jen wanted
			them on her half.  To each one's own.
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<date>07/29/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/7-29-07_800x600.JPG</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/7-29-07_120x90.JPG</thumbImg>
		<title>Garlic Butter, Fresh Basil Leaves, Mozzarella, Sliced Chicken Breast,Red Onion, Green Bell Pepper, and Roasted Red Pepper</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Yeah, this pizza was good.  I took the leftovers to 
			work - that was really a good pick-me-up.  I love the
			smell of the fresh basil combined with the roasted
			red peppers - it reminds me of when I used to work in 
			a pizza kitchen. 
			We got the basil, chicken, red onion, and green pepper 
			at the local farmer's market.  I could be imagining things,
			but it always seems like the produce there just tastes
			better than the store-bought stuff.
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>07/15/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/7-15-07_800x600.JPG</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/7-15-07_120x90.JPG</thumbImg>
		<title>Marinara, Fresh Spinach, Mozzarella, and Kalamata Olives</title>
		<entryHtml>
			This very simple pizza is always a pleaser. I've taken
			to getting the olives from the olive bar at the grocery 
			store down the street.  It is much cheaper to buy them 
			from the olive bar, as I only get exactly as much as I need
			to make a pizza.
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>07/01/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/7-1-07_1_800x600.JPG</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/7-1-07_1_120x90.JPG</thumbImg>
		<title>Marinara, Fresh Basil, Fresh Mozzarella</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Fantastic, but not original.  That's ok with me. 
			I uploaded a picture of the pizza before I stuck it in the 
			oven.  You can see it there, sitting in the screen, in
			all of its pre-cooked glory.
			I put the basil leaves flat underneat the cheese, but 
			on top of the sauce.  This prevents them from drying out
			and burning and tasting really gross.
			This pizza burned the roof of my mouth.  Ouch. I was a 
			little too eager to eat this evening.  Somehow everytime I burn the roof
			of my mouth, Jennifer comes out unscathed. 
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>06/24/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/6-24-07_800x600.JPG</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/6-24-07_120x90.JPG</thumbImg>
		<title>Marinara, Fresh Spinach, Mozzarella, and Kalamata Olives</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Hell, we're not feeling to original this time.  Sometimes
			you just want something that you know is going to rock.  This
			pizza is becoming our old standby. I am extremely happy with the
			way this one turned out.  I am also happy about the fact
			that I had it with a huge glass of beer sitting in front
			of the television.  Is that heaven on Earth or what? 
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>06/10/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/6-5-07_2_800x600.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/6-5-07_2_120x90.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Barbecue sauce, mozzarella, chicken, green peppers, and white onions on wheat</title>
		<entryHtml>
			This was an amazingly delicious pizza.  It was Jen's idea
			to use this topping combination.  We used Sweet Baby Ray's 
			barbecue sauce, which is our favorite.  Then I seared a 
			chicken breast on the stove until it was just barely cooked 
			enough, cut it in thin slices, and slapped it on with 
			thinly-sliced green bell pepper and thick-cut chunks of
			white onions.  Mmmmm! I'm getting misty thinking about this
			one again. I've taken to mixing about half bread flour with 
			half whole wheat flour - I feel like I'm getting nicer, stretchier
			dough with the higher gluten in the bread flour, but retaining
			the wonderful taste of the whole wheat. 
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>05/26/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/5-26-07_3_800x600.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/5-26-07_3_120x90.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Marinara, fresh spinach, mozzarella, and kalamata olives on whole wheat</title>
		<entryHtml>
			After the last strange pizza, Jennifer and I were looking 
			for something a little more down-to-earth.  This pizza was a 
			welcome change from the apricot weirdness from last time.  We 
			both love kalamata olives.  I can't stress enough how much 
			better they are than those plain old green or black olives
			you get in a can.  But of course, they are a little pricey.
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>05/10/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/5-10-07_1_800x600.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/5-10-07_1_120x90.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Apricot sauce, artichokes, red peppers, and mushrooms on whole wheat dough</title>
		<entryHtml>
			If this sounds like one of those pizzas that might be 
			gross but is actually really good, it's not.  I was trying 
			to emulate a frozen pizza that Trader Joe's sells, but this
			was nowhere near as good.  In fact, it was downright weird. 
			I was not a big fan of it at all.  What went wrong? I'm not sure.  The
			apricot sauce was really just apricot jam - maybe that was 
			the first mistake.  It was much too sweet.  The flavors
			just didn't blend together like I thought they would.  But hey! 
			At least I tried, right? 
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>04/29/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/4-29-07_800.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/4-29-07_120.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Marinara, Fresh Basil, and Fresh Mozzarella on Whole Wheat Dough</title>
		<entryHtml>
			I used whole wheat dough on the last pie I made, 
			and it was delicious. You can't go wrong with a Pizza Margarita -
			though I used a marinara instead of fresh Roma tomatoes. 
			Whatever, it was ridiculously good. The cheese was a bit 
			runny; next time I'll use a firmer one. The fresh mozzarella 
			I had picked out was a little on the squishy side, and when it 
			melted and combined with the sauce, the pizza was kinda drippy.
			In the picture, you can see lighter spots where the cheese was 
			sitting on top of basil leaves and couldn't mix with the sauce. 
			That's how runny it was.
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>04/02/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/4-2-07_800.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/4-2-07_120.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Marinara, Mozzarella, Broccoli, and Roma Tomatoes on Whole Wheat Dough</title>
		<entryHtml>
			After the last greasy pizza, I was really eager to try 
			something a little more wholesome. This pizza turned out to be 
			just the right thing. The whole wheat dough was spectacular. I 
			used King Arthur wheat flour. In combination with a spectacular 
			marinara sauce, fresh broccoli, and roma tomatoes, this pizza was 
			a major success. I think I will go for this combination more often.
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>03/21/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/3-21-07_800.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/3-21-07_120.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Garlic butter, ham, pineapple, green peppers, mozzarella, and goat cheese</title>
		<entryHtml>
			This was an ok pizza - not the best. It was very greasy 
			for some reason - I suspect it was a combination of the goat 
			cheese, mozzarella, and ham. I used a very low-quality pre-cut, 
			packaged ham for this pizza, and I'm sorry I did that. Next time 
			I will use a deli ham or Canadian bacon. Or maybe even prosciutto...
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>02/25/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/2-25-07_800.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/2-25-07_120.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Rosemary garlic sauce, sun-dried tomatoes, fresh mozzarella, and sauteed onions</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Actually, the sauteed onions were only on half of the 
			pizza, as Jen doesn't like onions particularly. This was 
			one of those \"what do I have in the kitchen to make a pizza?\" pizzas. 
			We really didn't plan the ingredients. Surprisingly, the crust on this 
			one was fabulous. 
			Here's a tip: always rehydrate sun-dried tomatoes 
			before putting them on your pizza. Soak them in hot water for ten minutes 
			and then drain. Additionally, make sure you put them underneath any other 
			toppings - unless you like the texture of leather on your pizza.
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>02/12/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/2-12-07_800.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/2-12-07_120.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Garlic butter, mozzarella, pineapple, goat cheese, and green peppers</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Yet another of the same. The crust came out pretty good on 
			this one - the bottom was nice and crispy, and the crust was 
			chewy and tasty in general. We used some of that generic mozzarella, 
			which is really not that tasty - at least not as tasty as real, fresh 
			mozzarella. Whatever, the pizza was still good.
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>01/28/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/1-28-07_800.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/1-28-07_120.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Garlic butter with oregano, mozzarella, portabella mushroom caps, and vine-ripened tomatoes</title>
		<entryHtml>
			This pizza was pretty good. I used a different kind of 
			yeast for this one (Red Star) because the store was out of 
			the kind I like (Fleischmanns). I'm not a big fan of Red Star 
			yeast; it just doesn't impart any flavor. Not that Fleischmanns 
			has tons of flavor, but at least it has some. Also, the dough was 
			a little flat, though I don't really care about that.  
			Portabellas are great on pizza - they have that wonderful 
			musky taste that really adds a depth of flavor unique to them. 
			They are complemented well by tomatoes, goat cheese, feta, 
			artichoke hearts, Italian sausage, and many other common pizza toppings. 
			I chose vine-ripened tomatoes for this particular pizza. 
			This pizza turned out exceptionally well. Two thumbs 
			up from Jen.
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>01/21/2007</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/1-21-07_800.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/1-21-07_120.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Pesto, sun-dried tomatoes, mozzarella, roasted red peppers, and kalamata olives</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Don't touch my pizza with any other olive than a kalamata. 
			I like to buy the kind that haven't been pitted, because you 
			can save a few bucks that way. You have to do a little more 
			work to prep the olives, though. 
			Always hydrate sun-dried tomatoes first, and always put them under the cheese, 
			to avoid burning them or drying them out. No one likes leathery
			or burned sundried tomatoes. 
			This pizza turned out exceptionally well. Two thumbs 
			up from Jen.
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>12/30/2006</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/12-30-06_800.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/12-30-06_120.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Pineapple, green peppers, goat cheese, mozzarella, and garlic butter</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Another riff on Jennifer's favorite pizza topping combination. 
			This one was cooked at 500 degrees for about 9 minutes. Flavor-wise, 
			it was pretty good. I'm still looking for that extra umph in the dough, 
			though - it was a little bland.
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>07/14/2005</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/7-14-05_800.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/7-14-05_120.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Roma tomatoes, green peppers, mozzarella, and marinara</title>
		<entryHtml>
			This crust was made with bread flour, so I cooked it 
			at a lower temperature. The marinara was made from fresh 
			summer tomatoes - delicious!
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>07/07/2005</date>
		<largeImg>/images/pizzas/7-3-05_800.jpg</largeImg>
		<thumbImg>/images/pizzas/7-3-05_120.jpg</thumbImg>
		<title>Pineapple, ham, mozzarella, and garlic butter</title>
		<entryHtml>
			Wow, this one was good. I made this while Jennifer was 
			out of town, because she does not like ham.  There are two 
			approaches to putting ham on a pizza - putting it under the 
			cheese or on top of the cheese.  Putting it on top yields ham 
			that is a little crispy on the edges, which is yummy.  In this 
			case, I put the ham under the cheese - which kept the ham from 
			drying out in the oven. 
		</entryHtml>
	</entry>
</entries>
